All pirates searching for the treasure One Piece must brave the second half of the Grand Line.
These wild and dangerous seas are known as the New World.
Gold Roger and his crew were the only men to ever chart these waters and learn all the secrets they held.
For the rest of the pirates of the world, this has proven to be the end of the road, a graveyard of dreams.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body became rubber after eating the gum gum fruit, set sail into the New World with his faithful crew.
I will be the king of the pirates!
During their journey to the New World, Luffy and his crew arrive on Fishman Island, which is located 10,000 meters below sea level.
The Fishman Pirates, led by Hordy Jones and assisted by Vander Decken, plot to overthrow King Neptune.
It's not long before the Straw Hats get pulled into the conflict.
Will you just look?
The Noah's stopped!
The Sea Kings? Why?
Oh, Luffy!
You're losing so much blood from that wound!
We need to get you to a doctor!
Yeah, maybe...
It's okay, really.
Just as long as the ship is stopped.
I'm just glad everyone is safe now.
To the future! The path to the sun!
Princess Shirohoshi!
You can't imagine how long we see kings waited for you to be born into this world!
Waited for me?
This vessel was designed for us to pull it, can't you tell?
This responsibility has been passed down for as long as anyone can remember.
Then, is that the reason why the Noah is so large?
Yes.
Our queen appears once every several centuries, though we do not know why she always takes the form of a mermaid.
It's strange.
I wonder...
But we do know that ever since you were born, you have been our exalted queen.
Is she...?
Me?
Yes.
I don't understand it.
But I think...
Our sister is speaking...
With the Sea Kings.
Incredible.
Guards!
Please report!
What made the Noah stop moving?
Well...
Uh...
You're not gonna believe this, sir, but a bunch of Sea Kings just showed up out of the blue when they took hold of it.
And...
I'm not sure I understand what they're saying, sir.
But I guess they stepped in because they wanted to stop Luffy from smashing the Noah to pieces.
For whatever reason, that ship must be really important to them, too.
Your majesty.
Sea Kings.
So, it's finally awakened.
The power that can destroy this entire world.
Look.
The bubble's being absorbed by the island bit by bit.
He won't survive in the deep sea.
Quickly, Shirochi.
You must retrieve him.
Help me!
Help!
My brothers!
We should capture the culprits and quickly!
Right!
And sink in!
Noah...
What sort of secrets are you hiding?
.
If I didn't know better, I'd say that the human wearing the hat may not be impossible for
you to do any trouble.
Others, we should capture the culprits, and quickly!
Right!
That's sinking!
Noah, what sort of secrets are you hiding?
If I didn't know better,
I'd say that the human wearing the hat was able to hear us as well.
I doubt that.
It has happened before.
Not so long ago.
Oh, I remember.
Rayleigh, did you hear that voice just now?
You're crazy.
There's obviously nobody down here.
Who's there?
Why am I hearing strange voices at the bottom of the sea?
Show yourself now!
Quite mysterious.
Quite mysterious indeed.
I hope the straw hats are okay.
They'll be alright.
They're strong.
I wouldn't worry about them.
He's right.
Just trust them, okay?
I don't know.
Huh?
Ah!
Seeking's you!
And they're pulling the Noah!
Ah!
Please don't eat me!
The Noah is crumbling.
Can it be saved?
Can it serve its purpose?
Well...
I believe it could be saved if we had their help.
However...
This is a different age.
Then can it be repaired?
I certainly hope so.
The appointed time is approaching.
Minister of the Left, sir!
We have a report from inside the Ryugu Palace!
What's happening?
Well, the good news is we've located all the mermaids who were kidnapped!
It turns out they're right here on the premises!
Oh, thank goodness!
Please tell me they're alright!
Yes.
They said they're still feeling a bit disoriented, sir.
But they do remember what they're doing.
They're still feeling a bit disoriented, sir.
Bad news is the treasure chamber's been wiped clean.
They took it all...
Down to the last piece.
It's awful!
We even lost the tomate box, sir!
Oh, no!
No!
We even lost the tomate box, sir!
Your Majesty.
Someone seems to have robbed us during the commotion!
Stolen treasures do not concern us now.
Not moments ago, we nearly lost our entire Kingdom!
Hmm?
The best things to do at present is tell the citizens that the mermaids are safe...
The damage may be done, but we still need to clear the Straw Hat's names.
We must do the right thing.
We better make tracks! Run!
There's no way we'll be smeared if they catch us!
We're humans. It's not like this was our fight anyway.
Going somewhere?
Let us through!
Let's just use our bubbles to fly over his head.
Ha! Water shot!
I won't hesitate to shoot you if you try to get away.
Am I clear?
Never mind!
They're gonna kill us, Boss Jinbei.
Come on, please. You gotta let us out of here.
We only did this stuff because we were scared of holding his crew.
We are humans, you know.
This fish man civil war thing's got nothing to do with us.
Besides, tourism from human pirates is good for their economy.
So, uh...
Yeah, come on, man. Just let us go. Please!
The punishment may not be as terrible as you think.
Let us wait to hear the royal family's decision.
There is one fact of which we must make all of you aware.
The mermaids are safe.
And as for the Straw Hats, they were not involved in any way.
We humbly admit that mistakes were made in our investigation.
For the unrest that this has caused, we must apologize.
You know, I never doubted the Straw Hats for a second.
I knew it wasn't them from the start. I just didn't want to say anything.
Drop the act! We're all to blame. Look at us! We didn't trust them for a second!
Nah, we believed them all along, right?
Yeah!
Hey, that's not true!
Don't say that!
I heard what you said!
Me too!
Admit it. We all believed the Straw Hats were responsible.
We judged them. Just because they were humans!
Yeah, you're right. We've always been like that. I feel awful.
Super Afro!
Look at that! It's just like mine!
Yeah, only cooler!
Chopper? You're not looking so good!
Nah, I'm okay!
Oh!
Thanks, Robbie.
Good grief.
It's because I used Monster Point, that's all. That one wears me out.
I won't be able to walk for a few hours, but I can still treat your injuries, slowly.
Now who's hurt? Let me take a look.
Worry about yourself first.
It looks like everyone here is fine.
Except for me!
After all that fighting, I need to rest my head too!
Only your lap can heal me, please!
Rest it up your ass instead.
If Robin wants me to!
What?
Luffy.
We made it!
Hey, look up here!
There they are!
We're back!
The princes are here!
I'm so glad they're okay!
It's Hordy and Deccan!
We've returned.
We're sorry we worried you, Father.
All that matters is that you're safe.
Now let's get them locked up.
Right!
Hear me, citizens!
There is no need to fear!
Never again will these villains cause trouble for our kingdom!
Whoa!
Has this been a crazy day or what?
What a terrible monster, that is!
And to think he was right here in our neighborhood!
Captain Hordy?
What happened to you?
We showed him his boss!
He-jangjh-jangjh-jangjh-jangjh!
I know that voice.
That's the princess!
Seems she's okay!
Hey!
Luffy!
I know that voice.
That's the princess! Seems she's okay!
Hey! Luffy!
Look, it's the princess and Straw Hat Luffy!
Someone help! I don't know what to do!
He won't stop bleeding!
I'm afraid he's going to die!
Whoa! Luffy! Hang in there!
Uh-oh!
Luffy's so brave! He could have died out there, fighting for us!
I hope he's okay.
This looks bad, but I've got a few hemostatics here in my bag.
Thanks a lot, Robin.
Sure.
Whoa! Is that new form really worth doing this every time?!
Right! Here we go!
Let me help you move...
What? What kind of doctor are you?!
A little loved. There.
Oh, doctor! Tell me Luffy's going to be all right!
I can stop the bleeding, but he's lost an awful lot of blood.
He needs a donor!
Well, that's no good. Luffy's the only one of us with Type F.
So we can't do it?!
There's gotta be someone who can!
Somebody!
Help us!
We just need one person to donate some blood!
We're begging you! Somebody here has to be Type F!
Really? Not a single one of you!
I... I'm Type F!
I'm the right type, but...
Papa! You're Type F, right?
Well, I, uh...
Oh, right! I forgot in this country there's actually a law against donating blood to humans!
What?!
What kind of law is that?! It's cruel!
Oh, come on! This guy just saved you!
I'd like to help, but I'm afraid my blood is in Type F!
It is red, though! Is that good enough?!
That's not really how it works, but thanks!
Princess Shirooshi...
Wait a sec! Maybe the human pirates can help him!
You've gotta be kidding me! Can't you do this one thing for the guy who saved this whole island?!
Huh?
You can give him some of my blood!
It's Type F!
Take as much as you need!
Wow, really?
Thanks, Jinbei.
Wait, but the law.
What of it? I'm a pirate.
Boss Jinbei, you're the best.
Go, Jinbei!
Wonderful.
Wait, Jinbei, if you...
It's all right.
But your majesty...
What makes it so wrong?
It's precisely that kind of thinking
that caused this to begin with.
Okay, let's do this.
I'm strong enough to move,
at least for a little while.
Can I help you somehow?
Sure, thanks.
It might sting a little, okay?
I can take it.
It's okay.
Okay.
Mm-hmm.
If you harm someone...
Or if someone harms you...
The same red blood is spilled.
And this tube through which that blood flows...
Small and fragile though it is, provides a pathway...
Through the prejudice that divides us...
And the conflicts that we create...
As though they were never there at all.
And more than any fleeting dream or fantasy could...
This path can guide us to the surface...
Into the warm light of the sun.
Luffy!
Jinbei.
You scared me!
Luffy!
You rascal.
So you were awake.
He's okay!
Yay, Luffy!
You see, Mother?
We made it.
Back to Sira.
Hey, Jinbei.
I want you.
To join my crew.
Peace has returned, and a grand celebration with dancing and singing begins at the Ryugu Palace.
While the Straw Hats enjoy the party with the merfolk, Robin closes in on a piece of Fishman Island's secret history.
Realizing the truth behind Joy Boy and the ancient weapon Poseidon, she uncovers a chilling truth.
On the next One Piece, the secret revealed.
The truth about the ancient weapon.
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!